Simple text adventure called "The adventure of the barren moor"
In "The adventure of the barren moor" the player is in the middle of an infinite grey swamp. This grey swamp has few distinguishing characteristics, other than the fact that it is large and infinite and dreary. However, the player DOES have a magic compass that tells the player how far away the next feature of interest is.
The player can go north,south,east,or west.
 
Here is an example playthrough you might create
 
You awaken to find yourself in a barren moor.  Try "look"​
> look
Grey foggy clouds float oppressively close to you,
reflected in the murky grey water which reaches up your shins.
Some black plants barely poke out of the shallow water.
Try "north","south","east",or "west"
You notice a small watch-like device in your left hand. 
It has hands like a watch, but the hands don't seem to tell time.
 
The dial reads '5m'
>north
The dial reads '4.472m'
>north
The dial reads '1m'
>e
 
You see a box sitting on the plain.   Its filled with treasure!  You win!  The end.
 
final file